莫妮卡  厨房有哪些东西是我的
Monica, which of all of this kitchen stuff is mine?
这个开罐器
This bottle opener.
-还有呢  -他还是个磁铁哦
- And...? - And it's a magnet.
你看
Look at that!
多巧啊
How weird is that?
你要搬来跟我住
You're moving in with me...
而我正缺一个开罐器
...and you have the one thing l don't have.
在某种程度上  你让我变得完整
lt's like, in a way, you complete me.
-厨房  -什么
- Kitchen. - What?
你让我的厨房变得完整  室友
You complete me kitchen, matey!
-罗斯  我知道你在想什么  -什么
- Ross, l know what you're thinking. - What?
她搬去跟你住
That she's gonna move in with you,
然后爱上你  然后...
then fall in love with you, and then...
当她发现你们还有婚姻关系
...when she finds out you're already married,
就会很高兴
she'll just be happy.
你真的很可怜
You know? You're just very sad.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我终于知道了
l see what this is.
你爱上瑞秋了
You are in love with Rachel!
-你瞎说什么  -没错  这就对了
- What?! - Of course, it all adds up!
你肯定是迷恋她
I mean, you're obsessed with her.
你总在问"瑞秋的事怎么办
lt's always: "What will you do about Rachel?
你为何要跟瑞秋住
Ross, Why are you moving in with Rachel?
你何时跟瑞秋承认没办注销的事"
When will you confess your secret marriage to Rachel?"
你分明是想要她
You want her!
不是
No!
电话救了你一命
Saved by the bell.
你好
Hello.
瑞秋  这对烛台不是我的吗
Hey, Rach, aren't these candlesticks mine?
不  那是我买的
No, no, l bought those.
-对  我忘了  -没事
- Oh, right. l forgot. - Yeah.
忘了你是个骗子
That you're a liar!
不会不会  太好了
No, no, that's great!
那我周一过去  再次谢谢你  再见
l'll be there Monday. And thank you again. Okay.
是古生物学的系主任  来自
That was the head of the paleontology department...
纽
...at N...
约
...Y...
大学
...U.
哇  他
Wow. What...
说
...did he...
什么
...say?
记得我去年发表的那篇
Remember that paper l had published last year
沉积速率的论文吗
on sediment flow rate?
-他们很喜欢  -有谁会"不喜欢"啊
- They loved it. - Well, who wouldn't?
就是
l know!
总之他们要聘我当客座教授
Anyway, they asked me to be a guest lecturer.
虽然现在是暂时的  但表现得好
l mean it's temporary, but if they like me,
就可能转任正职
it could lead to a full- time job.
标在信箱上多帅啊
How great would that look on the mailbox?
盖勒教授
Professor Geller.
是啊  教授与夫人
Yeah, Professor and Mrs.
与夫人
And Mrs.?
你和罗斯还是夫妻
Yeah, you know, you and Ross are still married.
什么
What?
开玩笑的啦
Just kidding!
吓死我了
Oh, God!
救了你的狗命
Saved your ass.
-怎么了  -我...
- What's the matter? - Well...
-我不是有在找灵媒吗  -是啊
- You know that psychic l see? - Yeah.
她说我这个星期会死
Well she told me l'm gonna die this week,
所以我为此有点沮丧
so l'm kind of bummed about that.
-什么  -我知道你们不太懂通灵术
- What? - Yeah, l know you don't know about psychic readings,
但这应该算是最糟的预言了吧
but that one is pretty much the worst you can get.
菲比  这太夸张了
Phoebe, that's crazy.
真不敢相信她会咒你死
I can't believe taht she'd say that to you?
亲爱的  你不会相信她说的吧
Honey, you don't believe her, do you?
不知道  她预言过我会生三胞胎
l don't know. She said that l'd have triplets...
但她也说其中一个是黑宝宝
...but she also said one of them would be black.
纯属好奇  她有提到死法吗
Just out of curiosity, did she say how you'd go?
不  她直到快结束了
No, she didn't tell me l was goanna die
才跟我说我会死
till the very end of the session.
我不想再跟她多耗一小时问问题
l wasn't gonna waste a whole other hour there!
我只剩一星期了
l've only got a week left, you know.
我真的得开始享受人生了
l've really gotta start living now!
大家好
Hey, everyone.
我今天第一次上课
Well, today's my first lecture...
有点想找你们演练一下
...and l kind of wanted to try it out on you guys.
可以吗
Do you mind?
-好啊  乐意之至  -当然可以
- No, that'd be great! - Sure.
"沉积速率
"There are three primary theories
有三个主要理论
concerning sediment flow rate.
每一个
Each of these theories
还可以细分为两个... "
can be further subcategorized into two..."
没错  我就是无聊致死的
This is it. This is what's gonna kill me.
"类别
" ...subcategories.
-第一个类别是...  -打住  罗斯
- The first of these subcategories is- - " - Stop, Ross.
你那张纸上有裸女吗
Are there naked chicks on that piece of paper?
没有  怎么了
No. Why?
我只是没见过有人会这么死命
l never seen a guy stare so hard at a piece of paper
盯着一张没裸女的纸
that didn't have chicks on it.
好的  我懂了
Oh, okay, okay.
"沉积速率
"There are three primary theories...
有三个主要理论
...concerning sediment flow rate.
每一个
Each of these theories...
还可以细分
...can be further subcategorized...
为"
...into- - "
你为什么不以笑话开场
Why don't you open with a joke?
以笑话开场啊
Open with a joke?
那是大学  可不是喜剧俱乐部
lt's a university, not a comedy club.
等一下  且慢
Wait a minute, hold the phone.
你说的不是咯咯窃笑大学吗
You're not talking about Chuckles University?
好吧
Okay.
我们跟你开玩笑的啦
Come on, we're kidding.
罗斯  你知道怎样会比较不无聊吗
Ross, hey. You know what might make it less boring?
谢谢"夸奖"
Thank you.
运用影像辅助
Some visual aids.
你知道哪种影像辅助最好
You know what's a good visual aid?
千万别跟我说是裸女
Please don't say naked chicks.
为什么不行
Why not?
我真是吃饱了撑的  才会跑来找你们商量
l don't even know why l bother to talk to you guys about it.
算了  我还是自行解决吧
You know l'm just gonna do it on my own,
不靠裸女
with no naked chicks.
我19岁之前  都是那样"解决"的
That's the way l did it till l was 19.
有有用的信吗
Any good mail?
有  演员工会寄信给你
Yeah. Something from the Screen Actors Guild.
可能是重播费
lt's probably a residual check.
你能帮我拆一下吗  我...
Can you open it? l got....
"保险中止"
"Benefits lapsed."
怪了
That's weird.
我不记得我演过叫这个名字的电影
l don't remember being in a movie called Benefits Lapsed.
这不是支票
lt's not a check.
你的医保失效了  因为...
It says your health insurance expired because...
你去年的工作时数不够
...you didn't work enough last year.
-我看看  -好的
- Let me see that. - All right.
真是难以置信
Oh, l can't believe this!
太过分了
This sucks!
有保险时  我可以被公车撞
When l had insurance, l could get hit by a bus...
或是被火烧
...or catch on fire, you know?
以前都无所谓  现在却得小心
And it wouldn't matter. Now l gotta be careful?
我很遗憾  伙计  被火烧这种事...
l'm sorry, man. There's never a good time to have to...
不能做了的确很遗憾
...stop catching on fire.
好吧
All right, well...
看来我得找份工作了  我去见经纪人了
...l guess l gotta go and get a job, I'm goanna see my agent.
好的  过马路前要记得左右看哦
Okay, make sure to look both ways before you cross the street.
"过马路前要记得左右看哦"  看屁啊
"Make sure to look both ways before you cross the street."
哇  菲比  你还活着啊
Hey, Pheebs, you're still alive!
感觉如何
How are you feeling?
等死的感觉好累喔
lt's so exhausting, waiting for death.
对了  你能不能...
Oh, by the way, do you think you- -
菲比  你干嘛呢
Pheebs, what are you doing?
我帮你为我的死亡做好心理准...
I was preparing you for my dea...
你刚没有以为我死了吗
Didn't you think l was dead?
我装得不像吗
Did that not come off?
像  我吓死了
Yeah, scared the hell out of me.
还以为我们要永别了呢
l thought we'd lost you forever.
-你要不要睡一下  -好  谢谢
- Pheebs, you wanna lie down? - Yeah, thanks.
对了  你能帮我个忙吗
And listen can you do me a favor?
两个小时后叫醒我哦
Can you just wake me up in a couple hours.
如果还叫得醒的话
You know, if you can.
莫妮卡
Monica.
这是你拿回去的吗
Did...did you take these back?
当然不是
No, no.
我很喜欢  就出去再买了一对
l just, I liked them so much that l went out and bought some for myself.
-真的很好看对吧  -对啊
- They're really great, aren't they? - Yeah.
我好喜欢哦
l love them.
想得美
Nice try.
课上得怎样
How'd the lecture go?
很顺利
lt went great.
既不需要笑话
And l didn't need any jokes
也不需要裸女
or naked chicks either.
太好了  罗斯
That's great. Ross.
抱歉之前没有好好帮忙
l'm sorry we weren't more supportive before.
我就知道教材充实最重要
l knew l just had to let the material speak for itself.
每个人都说
Everyone's all,
"罗斯  你得表现得既风趣又性感"
"Ross, you have to be funny and sexy."
我证明他们错了
Well, l proved them wrong!
我现在就去告诉乔伊和钱德勒
And now l'm gonna pass the news on to Joey and Chandler.
-说你既不风趣也不性感吗  -没错
- That you're not funny or sexy? - That's right!
-艾丝特尔  听着...  -哎哟  哎哟
- Hey, Estelle, listen--  - Well, well, well.
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
舍得回来了  是吗
So you came back, huh?
人人都以为离开这会更好  结果都
They think they can do better, but they all...
爬回来求艾丝特尔
...come crawling back to Estelle.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我哪有离开
l never left you.
你一直是我的经纪人啊
You've always been my agent.
-是吗  -对啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我没恶意  你别在意
Oh, well, no harm no foul.
你得帮我找点工作
Look, you gotta get me some work.
我的医保没了
l lost my health insurance.
好  首先要做的第一件事是
All right, first thing we gotta do:
伤害控制
damage control.
-为什么  -我觉得
- Why? - Well, l think...
可能有人
...someone out there...
在到处中伤你
...may have been bad-mouthing you all over town.
混账
Bastard!
明天艾丝特尔帮我排了一堆试镜
So Estelle lined up a bunch of auditions for me tomorrow.
我很快就能重新加入医保
And l'll have my health insurance back in no time.
太好了  但...
That's great, but...
你现在不应该去蹲马桶吗
shouldn't you be on the toilet right now?
-什么意思  -你是怎么了
- What? - What's wrong with you?
没什么啊
Nothing.
我刚才举哑铃时
l got this blinding pain in my stomach
肚子突然一阵剧痛
when l was lifting weights before.
然后就昏倒了
And then l passed out, and...
然后就一直站不起来了
...and l haven't been able to stand up since.
不过应该不怎么严重
But l don't think it's anything serious.
听起来像是疝气  你得...
This sounds like a hernia, you have to...
-去看医生 -不行
-Go to the doctor. - No way.
听着  就算怎么了要去看医生
Okay, look, if l go to the doctor for anything,
也是因为肚子这里突出来了
it'll be for this thing sticking out of my stomach!
那就是疝气
That's a hernia.
我为什么要恢复健身啊
Why'd l have to start working out again?
去你的  十五磅哑铃
Damn you, 15s!
我们来早了
Well, we're a little early.
还有15分钟才下课
The lecture doesn't end for 15 minutes.
-我们可以溜进去看啊  -对哦
- But we could sneak in and watch. - Yeah, we could.
看  KKD姐妹会的人
Hey, look. There's some Kappa Kappa Deltas.
我以前也是
l was a Kappa.
你好呀  姐妹
Hey, sisters.
我们以前还真是讨厌鬼
Wow, we really are bitches.
好  瑞格比从实验室
Right. So when Rigby got his samples
取回样本后
back from the laboratory...
他有个惊人的发现
...he made a startling discovery.
他原以为那是火山物质
What he believed to be igneous was,
其实是沉积物
in fact, sedimentary.
想象一下  他当时有多...
lmagine his consternation when- -
糟糕
Oh, bloody hell.
你在搞什么
What the hell are you doing?
我很紧张
Look, l was nervous.
你们害我担心我会很无聊
You guys had me all worried l was gonna be boring.
我走上讲台  学生们都盯着我看
l got up there and they were all, like, staring at me.
结果我一开口
l opened my mouth
就不由自主变成英国腔
and this British accent just came out.
的确  学得还很烂
Yeah, and not a very good one.
别再说了
Will you, please...?
盖勒博士吗  我是寇特·拉斯曼
Dr. Geller? Kurt Rathman.
我是古生物学系的教授
l'm a professor in paleontology department here.
你有时间跟我聊聊你的课吗
Do you have a moment to talk about your lecture?
抱歉  我和舍妹有约
l'm sorry, l've got plans with my sister.
我是莫妮卡·盖勒
Monica Geller.
是的  失陪一下
Right. Will you excuse us for one moment?
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
你能装英国腔  我就不能装吗
You can have an accent, but l can't?
小伙子  早啊
Top of the morning to you, laddies!
拜托你别闹了
Would you just please stop?
是的  这个季节的孟买  灰常怡人
Yes, yes, Bombay is very, very nice this time of year.
能帮我点个小煎饼吗
Hey, will you grab me a cruller?
坐下吧
Sit down!
我拜托你去医院吧
Will you go to the hospital?
疝气手术...
Dude, hernia operations cost like...
应该很贵  对吧
...a lot probably, okay?
而且它越来越黑  越来越痛
Besides, it's getting darker and more painful.
就表示有在好转
That means it's healing.
我借你钱
Look, l'll loan you the money.
赶快去医院
Just go to the hospital
把那玩意儿...
and let's just get that thing...
塞回去
...pushed back in.
心领了
Thank you,
但我要很久才能还你钱
but it'd take me forever to pay you the money back.
我不想老惦记着欠你钱
l don't want that hanging over my head, okay?
而且只要医保恢复
Besides, when my insurance kicks in...
我就可以动各种免费手术
...l can get all the free operations l want.
我打算先去做"激光眼"手术
l'll probably start with that laser eye surgery.
怎么了
What's going on?
乔伊的疝气很严重
Joey's got a really bad hernia,
不过动个"激光眼"手术就能搞定了
but it's nothing a little laser eye surgery won't fix.
真的  我告诉你
Look, l'm telling you,
把手压在肚子这里
if l put my hand on my stomach...
就不会疼得那么厉害
...it doesn't hurt that bad.
搞不好你会死
Hey, maybe you'll die!
钱德勒  我怕了
Chandler, l'm scared.
我们可以共赴黄泉
No, we can go together.
但不要拖太久  好吗
Just don't wait too long though, okay?
因为我星期五之前就会挂掉
Because l'm out of here sometime before Friday.
-但是我不想死  -别怕  会很好玩的
- But l don't want to die. - No, lt'll be fun.
我们可以回来吓唬他们
We'll come back and haunt these guys!
-给我  -不要  这是我的
- Give me them! - No, they are mine!
-是你偷我的  -是你偷我的
- You stole them from me! - You stole them from me!
拿来
Give me them!
要不要一人一个
Just wanna each take one?
很公平  反正也没用过
Yeah, that seems fair. We never use them.
听着  你们真的得帮帮我
Look, l really need some help, okay?
为什么  为什么我要装英国腔
Why? Why did l have to speak in a British accent?
我该怎么办
What do l do?
为什么不把口音改掉
Why don't you phase it out?
对啊  慢慢把口音改掉
Yeah, phase the accent out.
别人会以为你在适应美国的生活
People will think, you know, you're adjusting to life in America.
是啊  罗斯  根本不会有人注意到
Yeah, I mean come on, Ross. No one will even notice.
搞不好根本就没人听你在讲课
I mean they're probably not even listening to you.
没人听我在讲课吗
They're not listening to me?
当然有啦
Of course they're listening to you.
大家都在听你在讲课
Everybody listens to you.
莫妮卡
Monica,
你真的觉得我该试着慢慢改掉吗
do you think l should try this phasing-out thing?
我觉得你很帅啊
l think you look fine.
好了就开始吧
Whenever you're ready.
嘿  提米
Hey, Timmy.
我要给你
l've got a surprise...
一个惊喜
...for you.
停  抱歉
Hold it. l'm sorry.
这个惊喜是一组新秋千
The surprise is a new swing set.
别演得这么凝重
lf you could play it less intense.
好  没问题
Oh, yeah. Sure, no problem.
等我一下
Just hold on one second.
嘿  提米
Hey, Timmy.
我要给你一个惊喜
l've got a surprise for you!
天啊
Oh, my God!
所以我都喂我的狗吃"普瑞纳一号"
So that's why l feed my dog Purina One.
今天就搬一包回家吧
Pick up a bag today.
-这时候你要把它搬起来  -没错
- That's where you pick up the bag. - Exactly.
台词是"搬一包"
The line is, "Pick up a bag,"
所以你得把它搬起来
so you need to pick up the bag.
或是用指的
Or l could just point to it.
"普瑞纳一号"
Purina One.
今天就去指一包回家吧
Point to a bag today.
我没过  对吧
l didn't get it, did l?
-没过  -好吧
- No. - Yeah, okay.
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我来应征..."人"
l'm here to audition for "Man."
-你是说"垂死的人"吗  -正是
- You mean "dying Man." - Yes!
-再打一次  -真的要打吗   好
- Do it one more time. - Really? Really? Okay.
罗斯  你好  我是假口音大学的
Hello, Ross? This is Dr. McNeely
麦尼利博士
from the Fake Accent University.
我们想聘你当专职教授
We'd like you to come onboard full- time!
听我说
Listen to this!
预言错了  我不会死了
My reading was wrong. l'm not going to die.
真的   你怎么知道的
Really? How do you know?
因为我的灵媒死了
Because my psychic is dead!
她一定是看错牌了
She must have read the cards wrong.
我很遗撼
l'm sorry.
总比我死好
Better her than me.
我们来烤饼干吧
Hey, let's bake cookies!
恭喜你拿到这个角色
Listen, l'm really glad you got the part.
-你确定能演吗  -当然
- Are you sure you can do this? - Yeah.
谢谢你陪我来
And thanks for coming with me.
还有谢谢你帮我洗澡
And thanks again for helping me take a shower.
这样叫"再也不提"吗
Now, is that "never talking about it again"?
乔伊  我们都准备好了
Hey, Joe, We're ready for you.
这是亚历克斯  他演你的儿子
Joe, this is Alex. He'll be playing your son.
你好呀
Hi, Alex.
你们都看见了  我的手可没塞在裤子里
As you can see, my hands are not in my pants.
好的
Okay.
好  亚历克斯
All right, Alex. .
当乔伊说到...
Now, when Joey says his line..
"好好照顾你妈妈  儿子"
..."Take good care of your mama, son,"
"你就要哭  懂吗
that's your cue to cry. Got it?
好  开拍吧
All right, let's do this.
第五场  第一次
Scene five, take one.
开始
And action!
好好照顾你妈妈  儿子
Take good care of your mama, son.
拜托啦  儿子
Come on, son.
你妈是个好人
Your mama's good people.
卡  亚历克斯
Cut! Alex,
记住  这里应该要哭
remember, you're supposed to cry.
-你这次可以哭吗  -可以
- Can you cry for us this time? - Okay.
好  重来
All right. From the top.
第五场  第二次
Scene five, take two.
即将开始第三十六次
Take 36 is up.
好吧  再来一次
All right, let's try this again.
乔伊  你好了吗
You ready, Joe?
请问一下  你喊"开始"前
One thing, is it all right if l scream...
我可以大叫吗
...right up until you say, "Action"?
可以
Sure.
-开始  -好好照顾你妈妈.儿子
- Action! - Take good care of your mama, son.
停
Cut!
抱歉打断下  乔伊  你把衣服掀开来
l'm sorry. Why don't you lift up your shirt?
小鬼  你看
Take a look at this, kiddo.
小孩哭了
We have a crying child!
摄影机快拍
Roll the damn cameras!
-你好  -你好  请问罗斯在吗
- Hello. - Hello, is Ross there?
他不在  你要留言吗
No, he's not. Can l take a message?
是的  我是罗斯的离婚律师罗素
Yes, this is Russell, Ross' divorce lawyer.
麻烦转告他  既然一直没有他的回音
Just tell him that since l haven't heard from him,
我想他应该是想试着经营这段婚姻
l assume he's decided to give the marriage a try.
罗斯又结婚了
Ross got married again?
不会吧
No!
好的  继续
All right, keep going.
我要慢慢改掉口音
We are phasing the accent out.
改掉它
Phasing it out.
"要不是进实验室重新化验结果
"So without retesting their results in the laboratory...
研究小组也不会发现
...the team would never have identified...
原先的碳14定年结果
...the initial errors in their carbon dating...
有误"
...analysis."
到这里有问题吗
Were there any questions at this point?
-你说  -你的口音怎么没了
- Yes. - What's happening to your accent?
再说一次  你说什么
Come again? What's this nonsense?
好吧  我不是英国人
All right. l'm not English.
我是长岛人
l'm from Long lsland.
我当时十分紧张  结果一张口
l was really nervous, and the accent...
就变英国腔了
...just came out.
很抱歉
l'm sorry.
回到课堂上来
So if we could just get back to the lecture.
有任何问题吗
Were there any questions?
是关于古生物学的吗
About paleontology?
好吧  我当时只想留下良好的第一印象
All right, l was just trying to make a good first impression.
显然  我搞砸了
Obviously, l screwed up.
但你们对我的看法很重要
But what you guys think of me is important...
因为我想成为专职教授
...because l'm hoping to get a permanent job here.
如果你们肯再给我一次机会
So if you'd just give me another chance
留个好印象...
to make a good impression--
罗斯  你疯了吗
Ross! Are you crazy?
我居然还是你的老婆
l am still your wife?
你打算瞒我一辈子吗
Were you just never gonna tell me?
你脑子是不是进水了
What the hell is wrong with you?
我真想宰了你
l could just kill you!
瑞秋  你好啊
Well, hello, Rachel!
-你以前真的玩过吗  -对  当然啊
- You've really done this before? - Yeah, Yeah, Yeah.
你就用力一挥  知道吗
You just take a big, big swing, okay?
-不要手软  -好的
- Now, don't hold back. - Okay.
你们在干嘛
What are you doing?
我们在庆祝乔伊的医保恢复
We're just celebrating that Joey got his health insurance back.
好
Oh, all right.